<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Golang on Powerslacker</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/golang/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Golang on Powerslacker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Powerslacker</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 11:50:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/golang/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Interfaces Are Useless</title>
      <link>http://example.org/interfaces-are-useless/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 11:50:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/interfaces-are-useless/</guid>
      <description>When I first started using Go, one of the most confusing aspects was the interface type. I tried reading the source code of common interface definitions. I tried reading several tutorials. For a long time, I thought that interfaces were pointless, useless, and confusing.
The purpose of this article is to demonstrate that the interface type &amp;ndash; although useless &amp;ndash; is far from pointless and only slightly confusing. The interface through it&amp;rsquo;s uselessness, can be a powerful tool in the Go programmer&amp;rsquo;s arsenal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golang: A Synopsis</title>
      <link>http://example.org/golang-synopsis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 14:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/golang-synopsis/</guid>
      <description>This article is an attempt to coalesce the answers to many frequently asked questions on Golang I have seen floating around the net. I sense that many of the Go FAQ&amp;rsquo;s leave something to be desired in terms of the history of Go and it&amp;rsquo;s nature. I wanted to try my hand at a more robust introduction to Golang, that would give some context to the intention, history, and feel of the language and the community that has formed around it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RE: Moving From PHP to Go and Back Again</title>
      <link>http://example.org/re-moving-from-php-to-go-and-back-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 04:48:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/re-moving-from-php-to-go-and-back-again/</guid>
      <description>This post is a response to https://medium.com/@ivanjaros/moving-from-php-to-go-and-back-again-9ea1f57018c4
12/11/17, 11:51 PM - So, uh&amp;hellip;this post is blowing up on Hacker News. I haven&amp;rsquo;t posted in months and just got several months worth of traffic in a few hours. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if my ramblings are really more important than the MDN docs but special thanks to neoasterisk - whoever you are!
This post is top 3 on hacker news. Not bad for a random rant I threw together!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>