<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recent Posts on Powerslacker</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recent Posts on Powerslacker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Powerslacker</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 04:57:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hidden Costs of Neglecting Testing</title>
      <link>http://example.org/hidden-cost-neglecting-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 04:57:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/hidden-cost-neglecting-testing/</guid>
      <description>Programmers invariably agree: testing is a good thing. There have been studies that show that the earlier a bug is caught and repaired, the cheaper it is to fix in terms of both time and money. There are languages with testing baked in, there are testing frameworks, and even a testing movement whose apostles are borderline fanatics. Programming leaders espouse the virtues of testing and of having dedicated testers for software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MySQL Query Performance Optimization</title>
      <link>http://example.org/mysql-query-performance-optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 14:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/mysql-query-performance-optimization/</guid>
      <description>Its true that MySQL has performance limitations. However, for the majority of applications, MySQL&amp;rsquo;s performance limitations never get reached. Unless tables have several hundred million rows, or the application is using MySQL for an unintended purpose (full-text search, heavy analytics, etc.) then any performance issues faced are probably self-imposed via poor indexing, architecture, query composition, or application logic.
Don&amp;rsquo;t kick yourself for making any of these mistakes, as I&amp;rsquo;ve never met a developer who wasn&amp;rsquo;t guilty of at least one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interfaces Are Useless</title>
      <link>http://example.org/interfaces-are-useless/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 11:50:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/interfaces-are-useless/</guid>
      <description>When I first started using Go, one of the most confusing aspects was the interface type. I tried reading the source code of common interface definitions. I tried reading several tutorials. For a long time, I thought that interfaces were pointless, useless, and confusing.
The purpose of this article is to demonstrate that the interface type &amp;ndash; although useless &amp;ndash; is far from pointless and only slightly confusing. The interface through it&amp;rsquo;s uselessness, can be a powerful tool in the Go programmer&amp;rsquo;s arsenal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Takeaways: The Pragmatic Programmer</title>
      <link>http://example.org/pragmatic-programmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 14:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/pragmatic-programmer/</guid>
      <description>I first read The Pragmatic Programmer in 2017, after seeing it pop up in numerous online discussions as a must-read book for every programmer looking to hone their craft. I immediately saw what the hype was about. Now, nearly two years later I have begun perusing its pages once more, and it seems all the more relevant. Things that I missed in my first pass stand out to me, and I&amp;rsquo;ve lost count of how many tips mentioned in this book that I had to learn the hard way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golang: A Synopsis</title>
      <link>http://example.org/golang-synopsis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 14:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/golang-synopsis/</guid>
      <description>This article is an attempt to coalesce the answers to many frequently asked questions on Golang I have seen floating around the net. I sense that many of the Go FAQ&amp;rsquo;s leave something to be desired in terms of the history of Go and it&amp;rsquo;s nature. I wanted to try my hand at a more robust introduction to Golang, that would give some context to the intention, history, and feel of the language and the community that has formed around it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Converting from Wordpress to Hugo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/converting-wordpress-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 15:10:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/converting-wordpress-hugo/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, one of my posts &amp;ldquo;RE: PHP to Golang and Back Again&amp;rdquo; made it to the front page of Hacker News. It stayed at the third position on the front page for several hours, and was on the front page itself for no less than twelve hours! This was a major traffic boost for my blog, resulting in nearly thirty-thousand unique visitors in under two days. At one point, Google Analytics reported over one-thousand concurrent users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Years of Linux Mint</title>
      <link>http://example.org/2-years-linux-mint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 19:47:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/2-years-linux-mint/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been running Linux Mint as my daily driver for just over two years now. I want to lay out an honest review of my experiences using Linux as my main operating system (aka OS) so that interested persons can know what it&amp;rsquo;s like to switch from commercial operating systems, the pros and cons, and other tidbits about Linux as a desktop OS.
My Background I&amp;rsquo;ve been using desktop computers daily for roughly eighteen years, with a handful of days off for vacations and such.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RE: Moving From PHP to Go and Back Again</title>
      <link>http://example.org/re-moving-from-php-to-go-and-back-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 04:48:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/re-moving-from-php-to-go-and-back-again/</guid>
      <description>This post is a response to https://medium.com/@ivanjaros/moving-from-php-to-go-and-back-again-9ea1f57018c4
12/11/17, 11:51 PM - So, uh&amp;hellip;this post is blowing up on Hacker News. I haven&amp;rsquo;t posted in months and just got several months worth of traffic in a few hours. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if my ramblings are really more important than the MDN docs but special thanks to neoasterisk - whoever you are!
This post is top 3 on hacker news. Not bad for a random rant I threw together!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIX: Can&#39;t connect to local MySQL server through socket &#39;/var/run/mysqld/mysqld.sock&#39; (2)</title>
      <link>http://example.org/fix-cant-connect-to-local-mysql-server-through-socket/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 04:57:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/fix-cant-connect-to-local-mysql-server-through-socket/</guid>
      <description>Quick post today. This is more for my reference than anything else, but maybe some other soul on the web will need this info.
I recently installed the LAMP stack on my Linux Mint distro. Getting mysql to start was a struggle. The main terminal error was:
Can&amp;#39;t connect to local MySQL server through socket &amp;#39;/var/run/mysqld/mysqld.sock&amp;#39; (2).  I went through several Stack Overflow questions and none of the solutions were working out for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Currying, What is it? Why is it Useful?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/currying-why-is-it-useful/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 20:55:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/currying-why-is-it-useful/</guid>
      <description>Currying. It can be a frightening word. Textbook examples of currying appear to be hieroglyphics to the untrained eye. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t help that textbooks examples of currying use poorly named variables such as x, y, foo, and bar. I recently got a good grasp of the basics of currying and figured I&amp;rsquo;d share my understanding. Currying can be considered part of the functional programming (FP, for short) paradigm. The goal of functional programming is to make code:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Javascript with a Simple Project: &#39;Rock Paper Sccisors&#39;</title>
      <link>http://example.org/learn-javascript-simple-project-rock-paper-scissors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 18:46:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/learn-javascript-simple-project-rock-paper-scissors/</guid>
      <description>So you wanna learn Javascript? The best way to learn to code is by coding! In this tutorial series I’ll be training you on how to build ‘Rock, Paper, Scissors’ with Javascript.
You will learn the basic Javascript fundamentals so you can hit the ground running and build interesting projects of your own.
This series is aimed at absolute beginners – people who are new to Javascript, and are looking for a quick, but thorough introduction to JS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto Post to Craigslist</title>
      <link>http://example.org/auto-post-craigslist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 19:46:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/auto-post-craigslist/</guid>
      <description>Just completed this tutorial on how to build a web bot that automatically posts ads to craigslist using Nightmare.js
The goal of this guide is to teach you how to build web bots and web automation tools using Nightmare.js and avoid common pitfalls with proper planning, research, debugging techniques, and managing asynchronous code.
Video Playlist   Resources  nightmare.js pry.js vo.js artoo.js  Code main.js var Nightmare = require(&amp;#39;nightmare&amp;#39;), nightmare = Nightmare(); var vo = require(&amp;#39;vo&amp;#39;); var ads = require(&amp;#39;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Things Web Developers Need to Know</title>
      <link>http://example.org/10-things-web-developer-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 20:12:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/10-things-web-developer-designer/</guid>
      <description>I just finished creating a new web application called Only One Percent Listings. It was a medium sized project and really pushed the limits of my web development skills. I learned a lot and I wanted to document my experience for myself and pass that knowledge along for all the freelancers and junior developers out there.
Get Everything in Writing Developing a website or application with complex logic, solid front-end design, and thoroughly testing it is hard enough on its own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick and Easy Web Scraping Artoo.Js</title>
      <link>http://example.org/quick-and-easy-web-scraping-with-artoo-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 00:14:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/quick-and-easy-web-scraping-with-artoo-js/</guid>
      <description>I recently discovered a neat tool which you can use to scrape data from websites with relative ease, called Artoo.js. Artoo is a javascript library built to test web scraping in the browser, before implementing them in a dedicated scraper such as Sandcrawler.js or Phantom.js One of the great things about Artoo is that installation is dead-simple since its just a bookmarklet. You can go to the Artoo website and drag it to your bookmarks bar and you&amp;rsquo;re ready to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started with Nightmare.js</title>
      <link>http://example.org/get-started-with-nightmarejs-craigslist-screen-scraping-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2016 19:30:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/get-started-with-nightmarejs-craigslist-screen-scraping-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial you will learn to build a screen scraper using node.js, nightmare.js, and jQuery. This will scrape all the gigs posted on craigslist in the computers section for any city you choose. You can hook this up to a cron job and email yourself the results at regular intervals.
Video   Code Github repo
Dependencies sudo apt-get install node sudo apt-get install msmtp ca-certificates sudo apt-get install gnome-scheduler npm install --save jquery npm install --save nightmare -g  Configuring MSMTP http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>